{
    "subject": "resource/Jo_Van_Fleet",
    "predicate": "property/birthname",
    "object": "Catherine Josephine Van Fleet",
    "human_readable": "The birth name of Jo Van Fleet is Catherine Josephine Van Fleet.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9462596774101257,
            "question": "Who is Catherine Josephine Van Fleet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9427003860473633,
            "question": "What was the full birth name of Jo Van Fleet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939028799533844,
            "question": "What was Jo Van Fleet's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9368982911109924,
            "question": "What was the given name of Jo Van Fleet at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8610060214996338,
            "question": "If 'Jo Van Fleet' is an actress, what was her birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8282528519630432,
            "question": "What is Catherine Josephine Van Fleet better known as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7606115937232971,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Catherine Josephine Van Fleet and Jo Van Fleet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6785383224487305,
            "question": "Is 'Jo Van Fleet' the stage name of an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6775763630867004,
            "question": "How is Catherine Josephine Van Fleet identified professionally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6273674368858337,
            "question": "Did Jo Van Fleet use a different name professionally?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birth name of Jo Van Fleet is Catherine Josephine Van Fleet.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2472_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Catherine Josephine Van Fleet identified professionally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2472_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Jo Van Fleet' the stage name of an actress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2472_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Catherine Josephine Van Fleet and Jo Van Fleet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2472_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2472_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is mentioned in multiple files that Jo Van Fleet's birth name was indeed Catherine Josephine Van Fleet."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents support the statement that the birth name of Jo Van Fleet is Catherine Josephine Van Fleet. This information can be found in multiple files, such as `8.txt` and `91.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}